

AMRIZ JANTAN
Junior Full Stack Developer

## **ABOUT ME**

Certified Full Stack Developer with analytical and creative skills in addition to strong entrepreneurship. Multidisciplinary background with 7+ years experience in business modelling, branding and management that include both physical and digital operations as Co-founder of a Japanese lifestyle store. 9 years of experience in the corporate environment as a Senior Risk Analyst, responsible for complex risk assessments and key corporate clients' advisory.

Open to remote roles.

Portfolio:

amrizjantan.github.io/Portfolio-Revamp

Linkedin: @amriz jantan

Github: https://github.com/amrizjantan

N. Sembilan, Malaysia

+49 017632282463

Beckstraße 2
Hamburg Hamburg, Germany

### **LANGUAGES**

Bahasa Malaysia: Native

English: Expert

German: Advanced

Japanese: Intermediate

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

July 2021 - present

# JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER Freelance

Hamburg and Berlin, Germany

- Jointly responsible for developing www.bluesleeve.de a fully responsive webshop, both design and technical requirements using Wordpress technology.
- Webshop maintenance.

#### November 2014 - present

**CO-OWNER** 

Bluesleeve www.bluesleeve.de

Hamburg, Germany

- Assumed full responsibility in overseeing all aspects of business with focus on business development and create conceptual business module, plans and goals to ensure maximum profits with minimal risk.
- Oversee daily operations of retail store and online.
- Collaborate with artists and designers on art exhibitions and business projects.
- Responsible business tax preparation, bookkeeping, payroll and general accounting.

### January 2008 - October 2013

## RISK ANALYST Aon Corporation

Hamburg, Germany

- Risk assessment and advisory for diverse financial services and public listed multinational companies emphasizing on political, financial and management risks as well as crisis management framework.

## **EDUCATION**

2022

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM Career Foundry, Web Development

Berlin, Germany

2002

BACHELOR'S DEGREE
MARA University of Technology, Risk Management

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

## SKILLS

